Capital District Regional Planning Commission; Records apap380
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Rensselaer County, 1937-2003; 3; 8.01 cubic ft.
  This series contains files pertaining to planning decisions in Rensselaer County, New York. A significant portion of the documents cover decisions at the county level, including a county master plan, county housing studies, and information on county land use. There are also numerous files dealing with planning decisions in specific municipalities -- villages, towns, and cities -- including local waterfront revitalization program documents, environmental impact statements, land subdivision regulations, a proposed charter for the City of Troy, as well as details concerning the Troy Rehabilitation & Improvement Program (TRIP).
  - [Town of] Berlin, Capital Budget and Basis for an Official Map for Berlin, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - [Town of] Berlin, Proposed Land Use Control Map, 1971 July (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - [Town of] Brunswick, 1971 Summary, 1971 June (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - [Town of] Brunswick, Brunswick Celebrates 175 Years, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - [Town of] Brunswick, A Comprehensive Plan, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - [Town of] Brunswick, Conservation Advisory Council Annual Report, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - [Town of] Brunswick, Draft Comprehensive Plan, 2000 February (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - [Town of] Brunswick, Land Subdivision Regulations, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - [Town of] Brunswick, Site Plan Review Act, [Brochure], Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - [Town of] Brunswick, Zoning Ordinance, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - [Village of] Castleton, A Village Walk, 1977 June (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - [Village of] Castleton-on-Hudson, Basis for Comprehensive Planning, 1970 November (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - [Village of] Castleton-on-Hudson, Castleton Development Plan: Objectives and Policies for Future Development, 1971 March (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - [Village of] Castleton-on-Hudson, Initial Housing Element, 1970 August (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - [Village of] Castleton-on-Hudson, Local Waterfront Revitalization Program, 1987 May (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - [Village of] Castleton-on-Hudson, Local Waterfront Revitalization Program, 1996 January (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - [Village of] Castleton-on-Hudson, Proposed Revisions to Subdivision Regulations, 1969 April (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - [Village of] Castleton-on-Hudson, Zoning Regulations, 1984 March (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - [City of] Cohoes, Cohoes Central Area, 1973 March (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - [Town of] East Greenbush, Community Concepts and Development Planning: Their Application to East Greenbush: N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - [Town of] East Greenbush, Comprehensive Development Plan, 1970 July (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - [Town of] East Greenbush, The Comprehensive Zoning Law, 1999 August (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - [Town of] East Greenbush, Expansion of Pollution Control Facility, Engineer's Report, 1970 July (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - [Town of] East Greenbush, Land Development Policy, 1972 May (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - [Town of] East Greenbush, Land Subdivision Regulations, 1986 June (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - [Town of] East Greenbush, Open Space, Conservation Advisory Council [Brochure], Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - [Town of] East Greenbush, Planning Management and Recommended Zoning Changes, 1973 December (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - [Town of] East Greenbush, Proposed Couse Sewer Improvement, Engineer's Report, 1970 February (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - [Town of] East Greenbush, Re: East Greenbush Town Park, [Correspondence], 1973 February (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - [Town of] Grafton, A Comprehensive Plan, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - [Town of] Grafton, Site Plan Review Ordinance, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - [Town of] Grafton, Subdivision Regulations, 1968 May (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - [Town of] Hoosick, Draft Environmental Impact Statement, NY7 VT9 US7, 1987 October (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - [Town of] Hoosick, General Plan, 1967 April (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - [Village of] Hoosick Falls, General Plan for the Town of Hoosick and the Village of Hoosick Falls, Background Report, 1966 June (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - [Village of] Hoosick Falls, Government Efficiency Consolidation Project, Final Report, 1974 March (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - [Village of] Hoosick Falls, Intercepting Sewers, Pumping Stations and Sewage Treatment Plant, Revised Final Report, 1966 May (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - [Village of] Hoosick Falls, Sewage Treatment Plant Grading Plan, 1966 April (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - [Town and Village of] Nassau, Comprehensive Plan, (1 of 2), Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - [Town and Village of] Nassau, Comprehensive Plan, (2 of 2), Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - [Village of] Nassau, Nassau Pocket Park, 1988 Preliminary Application Municipal Park Projects, 1988 June (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - [Village of] Nassau, Nassau Pocket Park, 1989 Preliminary Application Municipal Park Projects, 1989 September (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - [Town of] North Greenbush, Amendment to Master Plan and Environmental Assessment Report for the RPI University Park, 1981 July (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - [Town of] North Greenbush, The Department of State Follies: A Technical Fiasco Completely Off-Key, [Memo], 1981 September (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - [Town of] North Greenbush, The Highlands Project, 1971 June (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - [Town of] North Greenbush, Land Subdivision Regulations, 1976 May (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - [Town of] North Greenbush, Local Waterfront Revitalization Program, 1989 September (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - [Town of] North Greenbush, Local Waterfront Revitalization Program, 1991 April (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - [Town of] North Greenbush, North Greenbush, Master Plan and Environmental Assessment Report for the RPI University Park, 1981 April (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - [Town of] North Greenbush, Preliminary Comprehensive Plan, 1974 March (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - [Town of] North Greenbush, Regional Prospectus for a High Technology Industrial Park, 1981 May (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - [Town of] Poestenkill, Re: Poestenkill Capital Improvement Program [Correspondence], 1970 January (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - [Town of] North Greenbush, Re: State Environmental Quality Review, Notice of Completion of Draft GEIS and Notice and Notice of SEQR Hearing [Correspondence] (1 of 2), 2003 September (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - [Town of] North Greenbush, Re: State Environmental Quality Review, Notice of Completion of Draft GEIS and Notice and Notice of SEQR Hearing [Correspondence] (2 of 2), 2003 October (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - [Town of] Poestenkill, The Summary Master Plan, 1970 February (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - [Town of] North Greenbush, Town Planning and Development Management, 1975 April (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - [Town of] North Greenbush, Transportation Project Report, I-90/Interchange 8 Connector to Route 4, Draft Air Quality Report, 1992 September (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - [Town of] North Greenbush, Transportation Project Report, I-90/Interchange 8 Connector to Route 4, Draft Noise Study Report, 1992 September (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - [Town of] North Greenbush, Water and Sewerage [Map], Undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - [Town of] Pittstown, Local Law No.3, Adopting Subdivision Regulations and Procedures, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - [Town of] Petersburg, Capital Budget and Basis for an Official Map for Petersburg, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - [Town of] Petersburg, Petersburg Water District Summary Report, Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - [Town of] Petersburg, Proposed Land Use Control Map, 1971 July (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - [Town of] Poestenkill, Re: Poestenkill Highway Plan Draft [Correspondence], 1969 September (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - [Town of] Poestenkill, Transportation-Community Facilities-Town Development, Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - [Town of] Pittstown, Proposed Land Use and Development Code, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - [City of] Rensselaer, Downtown Redevelopment Plan 2003-2010, 2003 June (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - [City of] Rensselaer, Environmental, Assessment, Proposed Coal-Fired Cogeneration Facility, 1989 January (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - [City of] Rensselaer, Housing Code, 1968 April (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - [City of] Rensselaer, A Local Management Case Study, 1979 April (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - [City of] Rensselaer, Local Waterfront Revitalization Program, 1988 September (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - [City of] Rensselaer, Master Plan, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - [City of] Rensselaer, The Rensselaer Riverfront: A Public Policy Guide, 1976 August (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - [City of] Rensselaer, Riverfront Development Plan, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - [City of] Rensselaer, Youth Needs Assessment, 1984 March (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Rensselaer County, An Alternative to Incarceration Proposal for Rensselaer County, 1985 March (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Rensselaer County, Analysis of Service Demand Potential, 1974 March (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Rensselaer County, Architecture Worth Saving, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Rensselaer County, Assorted Loose Documents, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Rensselaer County, Building Permit Activity in Rensselaer County 1987, 1988 September (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Rensselaer County, Rensselaer County, Capital Improvements Program Manual for Rensselaer County, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Rensselaer County, Castleton Island State Park Master Plan Report, 1989 September (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Rensselaer County, A Citizen's Guide to Local Governments' in Rensselaer County, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Rensselaer County, City of Rensselaer and Town of East Greenbush, Engineer's Report to Accompany Application to Water Resources Commission, 1965 January (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Rensselaer County, Comprehensive Sewerage Study: Village of Nassau, Town of Schodack and Environs, 1967 October (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Rensselaer County, Community Facilities Plan-Public Buildings, 1971 June (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Rensselaer County, Development Goals and Policy Statements, Preliminary Report, Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Rensselaer County, Development Policies and Planning Standards, 1969 February (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Rensselaer County, A Driving Tour of Rensselaer County, Undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Rensselaer County, Economic Development Guide, 1979 June (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Rensselaer County, An Economic Study of Land Utilization in Rensselaer County, N.Y., 1937 June (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Rensselaer County, Educational Facilities, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Rensselaer County, Eligibility Community Family and Children's Services [Brochure], Undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Rensselaer County, Existing Resources-Taconic Valley Area Part 1, 1971 February (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Rensselaer County, Existing Resources Taconic Valley Area Part 2, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Rensselaer County, Expanded Rensselaer County Sewer District, 1969 May (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Rensselaer County, Fiscal Analysis-Rensselaer County, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Rensselaer County, Formation of Rensselaer County Sewer District No. 1, 1967 June (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Rensselaer County, General Soil Map of Rensselaer County, 1966 May (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Rensselaer County, Government Preliminary Report, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Rensselaer County, The Ground-Water Resources of Rensselaer County, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Rensselaer County, Historic Preservation Plan/Policy, 1974 March (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Rensselaer County, Homesite Planning Guide, 1978 October (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Rensselaer County, Homesite Planning Guide, 1988 October (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Rensselaer County, Housing Study, 1974 January (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Rensselaer County, Human Resources Profile, 1978 March-1978 June (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Rensselaer County, Industrial Development Program for Rensselaer County [Proposal], 1977 March (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Rensselaer County, Industrial Resources Survey of Rensselaer County, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Rensselaer County, Initial Housing Element, Preliminary Report, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Rensselaer County, Joint Treatment Study, Troy Rensselaer and Environs, 1968 October (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Rensselaer County, Land Potential/Recreation Resources and Plan, Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Rensselaer County, Land Subdivision Regulations, Final Draft, 1975 January (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Rensselaer County, Land Use, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Rensselaer County, Land Use Analysis, 1968 December (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Rensselaer County, Land Use Plan/Policy, 1972 June (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Rensselaer County, Land Use Plan Proposals Preliminary Report, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Rensselaer County, Mental Hygiene Unified Services Plan, 1974 August (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Rensselaer County, Mental Hygiene Unified Services Plan (1 of 2), 1974 August (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Rensselaer County, Mental Hygiene Unified Services Plan (2 of 2), 1974 August (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Rensselaer County, Natural Areas of Rensselaer County, 1995 February (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Rensselaer County, Natural and Cultural Features Survey, Preliminary Report, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Rensselaer County, Natural Resource Inventory Handbook: A Usage Guide, 1988 April (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Rensselaer County, The Nucleus of the Northeast, [Promotional Booklet], 1985 June (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Rensselaer County, The Official Rensselaer County Building Permit Report of 1994, 1995 May (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Rensselaer County, Outdoor Recreation and Open Space Plan, 1971 May (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Rensselaer County, Overall Economic Development Plan, Undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Rensselaer County, The People of Rensselaer County, NY: Trends in Human Resources and Their Characteristics 1900-1960, 1968 August (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Rensselaer County, Planning Program Rensselaer County 1968-1972, 1969 February (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Rensselaer County, Profile of Rensselaer County, Undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Rensselaer County, Proposal for Planning in Rensselaer County, 1967 April (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Rensselaer County, Public Buildings, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Rensselaer County, Recreation, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Rensselaer County, Re: East Greenbush-Rensselaer Comprehensive Study Project #WPC-CS-109 [Correspondence], 1967 December (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Rensselaer County, Re: RPI High-Tech Industrial Park [Correspondence], 1981 July (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Rensselaer County, Rensselaer County [Promotional Booklet], Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Rensselaer County, Rensselaer County [Promotional Brochure from Rensselaer County Development Agency], Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Rensselaer County, Rensselaer County 175th Anniversary [Promotional Booklet], 1966 February (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Rensselaer County, Rensselaer County Bureau of Planning Policies Contained in Previous Reports, Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Rensselaer County, Rensselaer County Comprehensive Sewerage Study (1 of 2), 1978 September (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Rensselaer County, Rensselaer County Comprehensive Sewerage Study (2 of 2), 1978 September (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Rensselaer County, Rensselaer County Data Book, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Rensselaer County, Rensselaer County Does Its Part-Removes Pollution From the Hudson River [Brochure], 1976 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Rensselaer County, Rensselaer County Future [Report], 1970 November (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Rensselaer County, Rensselaer County Growth and Development, 1979 June (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Rensselaer County, Rensselaer County Housing Study, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Rensselaer County, Rensselaer County Industrial Development Agency, Undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Rensselaer County, Rensselaer County Land Use Element Summary, 1978 April (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Rensselaer County, Rensselaer County Legislature Regular Meeting, Presentation of Petitions and Communications, 1978 October (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Rensselaer County, Rensselaer County Legislature, Resolution to Amend the Budget of Hudson Valley Community College, 1978 October (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Rensselaer County, Rensselaer County Master Plan, Draft, 1989 July (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Rensselaer County, Rensselaer County Master Plan, Undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Rensselaer County, Rensselaer County Past and Present, 1970 November (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Rensselaer County, Rensselaer County Population, Analysis 1968/Projection 1990, 1969 January (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Rensselaer County, Rensselaer County Sewer District No. 1, Wastewater Facilities Report, 1970 March (Oversized 3)
  - Rensselaer County, Rensselaer Port Access Connector Roadway Locational Analysis Study (1 of 2), 1981 December (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Rensselaer County, Rensselaer Port Access Connector Roadway Locational Analysis Study (2 of 2), 1981 December (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Rensselaer County, Rensselaer Technology Park [Promotional Brochure], Undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Rensselaer County, Report of the Priorities Determination Committee, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Rensselaer County, Report of the Rensselaer County Master Plan Steering Committee, 1988 June (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Rensselaer County, Report on Comprehensive Public Water Supply Study, 1972 August (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Rensselaer County, Report on Comprehensive Sewerage Study Rensselaer-East Greenbush, 1966 December (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Rensselaer County, Report on Potential Needs for Community Garden Sites in Troy Cohoes, Green Island, Waterford, and Watervliet, 1988 June (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Rensselaer County, Report Rensselaer County Comprehensive Sewerage Study (1 of 3), 1979 January (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Rensselaer County, Report Rensselaer County Comprehensive Sewerage Study (2 of 3), 1979 January (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Rensselaer County, Report Rensselaer County Comprehensive Sewerage Study (3 of 3), 1979 January (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Rensselaer County, Revised Overall Program Design 1971-1974, 1970 December (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Rensselaer County, Route 7-Hoosick Street Bridge Development Impact Study, 1977 June (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Rensselaer County, Rural Rensselaer Committee on Health Access, 1990 May (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Rensselaer County, Rural Sewage Disposal, 1958 December (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Rensselaer County, Seventh Annual Industrial Forum, [Conference Informational Folder], 1982 October (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Rensselaer County, Social Indices and Housing, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Rensselaer County, Social Indices and Housing Preliminary Report, 1969 August (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Rensselaer County, Soil Survey of Rensselaer County, 1937 March (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Rensselaer County, Soil Survey of Rensselaer County, 1988 January (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Rensselaer County, The Strip: A Handbook for Developers and Municipalities, Undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Rensselaer County, The Subdivision: A Handbook for Developers and Municipalities, Undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Rensselaer County, Summary Report on Comprehensive Public Water Supply Study for Rensselaer County, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Rensselaer County, Taconic Valley Comprehensive Plan Part 3, 1971 June (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Rensselaer County, Taconic Valley Proposed Land Use and Development Code, 1971 June (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Rensselaer County, Transportation 1968, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Rensselaer County, Transportation Plan, 1973 October (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Rensselaer County, Transportation Analysis, 1979 July (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Rensselaer County, Water Resources in Rensselaer County, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Rensselaer County, Water Supply and Sewage Disposal, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - [Town of] Sand Lake, Board Meeting Minutes, 1985 December 11 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - [Town of] Sand Lake, Community Facilities, Undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - [Town of] Sand Lake, Draft Environmental Impact Statement for Tremont Lumber Company, Inc., 1985 November (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - [Town of] Sand Lake, Master Plan, 1993 September (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - [Town of] Sand Lake, Report on Comprehensive Sewerage Study, 1965 March (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - [Town of] Sand Lake, Subdivision of Land, Chapter 225 from the Code, 1997 March (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - [Town of] Sand Lake, The Summary Master Plan, Undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - [Town of] Sand Lake, Wastewater Facilities Report, 1974 December (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - [Town of] Schaghticoke, Preliminary Comprehensive Plan, 1975 April (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - [Town of] Schaghticoke, Zoning Law, Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - [Town of] Schodack, Comprehensive Sewerage Study, 1967 May (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - [Town of] Schodack, Final Environmental Impact Statement for Aspen Crest Subdivision, 1992 May (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - [Town of] Schodack, I-90 Impact Study, Final Report, 1975 February (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - [Town of] Schodack, I-90 Impact Study, 1975 October (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - [Town of] Schodack, Initial Housing Element, 1970 September (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - [Town of] Schodack, Plan of Study, 1977 February (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - [Town of] Schodack, Report on Formation of the General Sewer District, 1968 May (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - [Town of] Schodack, Schodack Central School District 2000-01 Resident Survey [Response Forms], 2001 April (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - [Town of] Schodack, Subdivision of Land and Design and Construction Standards, Chapter 188 (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - [Town of] Schodack, Subdivision of Land and Design and Construction Standards, Chapter 188 (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - [Town of] Schodack, Wastewater Facilities Plan Environmental Assessment, 1981 March (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - [Town of] Schodack, Zoning Law, 1990 January (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - [Town of] Schodack, Zoning Law Chapter 219, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - [Town of] Schodack, Zoning Law Chapter 219, 1998 May (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - [Town of] Stephentown, Capital Budget and Basis for an Official Map for Stephentown, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - [Town of] Stephentown, Ordinance for the Regulation of House Trailers and Trailer Camps, 1974 June (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - [City of] Troy, Bicentennial Troy, An Advertising Supplement to the Times Union, 1989 April (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - [City of] Troy, Building Code Administrative Section, 1961 June (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - [City of] Troy, Buyer's Guide and Membership Directory, Chamber of Commerce of Greater Troy, Undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - [City of] Troy, City of Troy, New York, Master Plan, 1962 June (Oversized 2)
  - [City of] Troy, Coastal Zone Management, Plan/Legislation, 1977 February (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - [City of] Troy, Comprehensive Assessment Report for the England City School District, 1985 September-1985 December (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - [City of] Troy, Cultural Resources Survey, Stage 1A, Oakwood Cemetery, 1990 January (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - [City of] Troy, Cultural Resources Survey, Stage 1B, Oakwood Business Park, 1990 June (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - [City of] Troy, Draft Environmental Impact Statement for New Elementary School Located at Detroit Avenue and Georgian Court, 1989 June (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - [City of] Troy, Draft Environmental Impact Statement for New Elementary School Located at Tibbits Avenue and Sunset Terrace, 1990 June (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - [City of] Troy, Draft Generic Environmental Impact Statement, Oakwood Business Park, 1990 August (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - [City of] Troy, Economic Data Survey of the Greater Troy Area, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - [City of] Troy, Environmental Site Assessment, Oakwood Business Park, 1990 February (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - [City of] Troy, Fall 1985 House Hunter's Guide, Undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - [City of] Troy, A Fiscal and Economic Analysis, 1981 December (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - [City of] Troy, Full Environmental Assessment Form, Oakwood Business Park, 1990 May (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - [City of] Troy, Historic Troy: A Downtown Tour [Brochure], Undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - [City of] Troy, Housing Plan, 1974 June (Box 7, Folder 35)